<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<profile>
	<question>
		<number>0.1</number>
		<answer>Chris Ding Dong
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.2</number>
		<answer>Anywhere, Anytime 
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.3</number>
		<answer>Business Administration (aka Capitalistic Asshole)
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>0.4</number>
		<answer>April 17, 1982
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.5</number>
		<answer>Usually .25 inches or shorter
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>1</number>
		<answer>My ultimate goal when I first joined was to slowly work my way up through the ranks of a student group on the UC Berkeley Campus and eventually take it over.  Well, it has happened, and now I have minions to do my bidding for me.  Oh ya, I also do it for the wonderful people, my love for the world of theatre, and the fact that I will never ever again have the chance to be with so many awesome people doing something I love this much ever again.  Unless Theatre Rice goes nationwide.  Then I can do this for a living.
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>2</number>
		<answer>When people think Chris Dong, I think an image of me in an apron madly waving a clever about is the first thing that comes to mind (aside from Capitalistic Asshole).  I spend most of my waking hours either doing things for Theatre Rice, homework, or COOKING/EATING. My love for food is beyond words.  I cook whenever I get the chance and always think about how to better improve upon the food that I eat and serve to others.  I love Mr. KitchenAid Mixer and Mrs. Henkels Santoku knife.  If anybody ever wants to get together and cook, drop me an email or something.  Other than Theatre Rice and cooking, I really don't have time for other hobbies, except for being the occasional nerd and busting out on my Playstation 2 or playing a good computer game.  But shhhh, you didn't hear that.
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>3</number>
		<answer>I live to see that others are happy, whether it be the members watching a Theatre Rice show, peoples eating the food I make them, making people laugh, or doing anything else I can to make their day brighter.  I also live with the hope of beating all the mean kids at Haas at their own game and being the first one out of the class of 2005 to make it on the cover of the Wall Street Journal.  For something good, not any of that accounting scandal crap.  That would be grand.
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>4</number>
		<answer>I love the song That it is to Burn by Finch.  It is 4:52 long and is 4.47 MB (at 128 Kbps and 44KHz).  I also listen to the entire Rent Soundtrack several times per week.  That is significantly longer and larger in size than That it is to Burn.
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>5</number>
		<answer>Eating a horrible meal (i.e. choking on a Big Mac, getting SARS from a taco supreme at Taco Bell, getting anthrax from a Grand Slam, eating a poisonous Whopper, etc.) 
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>6</number>
		<answer>If Theatre Rice acquired $923,157, I would first try to put a down payment on a new theatre for Theatre Rice (a real theatre that doesn't involve being a converted lecture hall).  I would build the theatre on top of Dwinelle so that Dwinelle would become even more confusing and the only way you could get to the theatre would involve going through a labyrinth of sorts, complete with a Minotaur (I think this would be the majority of the expenses).  If you could find your way through the labyrinth, you could get into the show for free.
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>7</number>
		<answer>Rot on the walls in the basement of my apartment building.  The rot ate away at the walls supporting the building, causing the walls in my building to shift down a bit, causing all the doors in my apartment building to misalign with the locks, causing the locks not to work too well.  Hence, rot on the walls in the basement of my apartment building is the most evil thing ever.  Period.
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>8</number>
		<answer>
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>9a</number>
		<answer>
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>9b</number>
		<answer>
		</answer>
	</question>

</profile>