<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<profile>
	<question>
		<number>0.1</number>
		<answer>Emi "It's-Not-Short-For-Emily" Ikkanda
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.2</number>
		<answer>Of The Feminine Gender
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.3</number>
		<answer>Doubling Art and English
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>0.4</number>
		<answer>11.20.84
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.5</number>
		<answer>In Between Medium and Mid-Way Length
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>1</number>
		<answer>Because I believe the world needs another Emi. On stage
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>2</number>
		<answer>Dangerous obsession with filmage. An average consumption of music, mostly of the rock persuasion. What?s that? Not vivid enough for you? FINE: &lt;br&gt;

My good friend Mr. TV: Gilmore Girls and most things on Comedy Central.
Bookage: Read the Princess Bride. And these authors: Amy Tan, David Sedaris, Louis Sachar.
Musica: Let?s just say that the best albums of 2003 were by the White Stripes, Outkast, Yeah Yeah Yeahs, and the Stokes.
Movies: Ack! I?ll say it again: Comedy: Dogma, Chasing Amy, Clerks, Monty Python and the Holy Grail, This is Spinal Tap, Princess Bride, About a Boy. Drama: Magnolia, Almost Famous, American Beauty, Good Will Hunting, Pleasantville, Lost in Translation. Romantic Comedy: Amelie, Bridget Jone?s Diary, When Harry Met Sally, Annie Hall, Sleepless in Seattle. Dorky Teen Flick: Clueless, Ferris Beulier?s Day Off, Breakfast Club. Classic: Sabrina, Casablanca, Some Like It Hot, The Apartment, Breakfast at Tiffany?s, Gold Rush. Musical: Moulin Rouge, Chicago. Sci Fi: Gattaca, Contact, Star Wars (The original trilogy, not the recent crap). Action Trilogy: Indiana Jones, Back to the Future. Movies for Guys Who Like Movies: Apocalypse Now, Taxi Driver, Pulp Fiction. Whew. And that?s not even the complete list.

		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>3</number>
		<answer>The meaning of life is to give life meaning. Erm, yeah. But for reals, I apparently live to write and art, hence the majors. I fancy myself a painter and novelist.
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>4</number>
		<answer>That is an evil question. As if I could whittle my entire musical tastes into a singular song. How dare you question me in such a manner! How about this: Best videos of 2003: White Stripes Seven Nation Army and Outkast?s Hey Ya.
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>5</number>
		<answer>Until my body is unable to house such a magnificent creature and decides to expire. Preferably after I complete my list of Things-To-Do-Before-I-Die.
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>6</number>
		<answer>Death by elven creatures attacking me with veggie peelers. Peeled to death ? that?s a bad way to go
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>7</number>
		<answer>
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>8</number>
		<answer>Um. Not. Me. ?
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>9a</number>
		<answer>What is your favorite two minutes of your favorite film?
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>9b</number>
		<answer>ASDKLJFALSKDFJKDLS;AJFKDLASJF!!! ::emi?s head explodes::
		</answer>
	</question>

</profile>