<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<profile>
	<question>
		<number>0.1</number>
		<answer>Julia Cho

		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.2</number>
		<answer>female
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.3</number>
		<answer>Rhetoric - and Theater, Dance and Performance Studies (TDPS)
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>0.4</number>
		<answer>Sure, why not?  i haven't had one in a while.  i get kind of nervous though, and i don't act like my usual self . . 
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.5</number>
		<answer>midway down my back.  It'll probably be shorter when i finally get curls
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>1</number>
		<answer>When i was a freshman, i had heard of it through a friend and decided to check out the validity of this otherworldly haven in which theatre and Asians coexisted.

		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>2</number>
		<answer>i like to eat.  A LOT.  It can be embarassing at times.  Throughout my life, i've been endowed with such nicknames as Piggy, Oink Oink, Seconds, and Garbage Disposal.  Hobby #2 varies from season to season.  Right now, i've returned to my drawing phase.
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>3</number>
		<answer>My family.  What can i say?  i'm a selfless person.  i mean, i guess i could say i live for myself but then who would i be without my family?  Viva la CHO!
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>4</number>
		<answer>At the moment, i love "Alphabet Song" by Goh Nakamura which fits within a neat 3 min 33 sec.  (Thanx to Hellen who introduced me to his music!)
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>5</number>
		<answer>Maybe somewhere around 250.  It's frickin' old but feasible, i think.  And being Asian and all, i'll probably look like a spry 180-year-old at the most.  It'd be kool to end up in the Guinness Book of World Records for something.

		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>6</number>
		<answer>
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>7</number>
		<answer>No, i wouldn't pilfer it.  i care about Rice too much.  (i'm selfless, remember?)  i'd buy us a much-needed warehouse and a bus and maybe our own theatre (even though 155 Dwinelle has its charms).

		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>8</number>
		<answer>i'm not sure which object is the most evil, but i'd venture to say my ghetto laptop comes pretty close.  The only reason i don't destroy it by beating with a baseball bat or throwing it out my window is that it's going to die on its own any second now.

		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>9a</number>
		<answer>
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>9b</number>
		<answer>
		</answer>
	</question>

</profile>