<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<profile>
	<question>
		<number>0.1</number>
		<answer>Kevin Phung
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.2</number>
		<answer>Male
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.3</number>
		<answer>Intended MCB
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>0.4</number>
		<answer>Spring 2004
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>0.5</number>
		<answer>not sure
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>1</number>
		<answer>I like the people too much to not do it again
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>2</number>
		<answer> I have a gambling problem.  Aside from that, I do Tae Kwon Do @ the RSF and hope to make it to Nationals with the rest of the team.
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>3</number>
		<answer> My family and myself... not necessarily in that order.  I haven't made up my mind yet.
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>4</number>
		<answer> Oh that's questionable too.  I really just have a "song-of-the-moment" that makes me feel good.  That would probably have to be "Something
Corporate - She Paints Me Blue" off their new album "North".  It's 3:38 minutes and 5.05 MB (CD-Quality).  If you don't know who Something Corporate is... they're an OC band.  If you don't know what the OC stands for... tune into Fox on Wednesday nights at 9pm.

		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>5</number>
		<answer> I live in the present... and if that present happens to extend into the future, so be it.

		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>6</number>
		<answer> With regret.
		</answer>
	</question>
		<question>
		<number>7</number>
		<answer>
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>8</number>
		<answer> I'm going to get a little political, so please bear with me.  I don't buy into the whole "evil vs. good"/"black vs. white" point of view that many Americans have embraced.  This bipolar ideology has led many Americans to prejudge and marginalize almost everything they come into contact with.  One explanation for this is because Americans like simplicity.  Who wants to talk about the grayness of exceptions and all that garbage?  It is simply easier to break things up into 2 categories.  For example, during the Cold War, all Russians/Communists were labeled as "evil".  We were the "good guys" and they were "the bad guys".  It was easy to manage, and it was even easier to repeat incessantly to the American public.  I just find it hard to believe that an entire country of people could be "evil".  Even though our governments insist on telling us how we are different from each other, I feel that we really have many things in common.  People are just that--people.  We all want to live happy and peaceful lives.  We all want to ensure the safety of our children's futures.  It just so happens that we are born into different geographical positions and forced to comply with the duties of citizenship.  American parents and Russian parents both have love for their children, but for some reason the Russian parents are amongst those labeled as cold-hearted monsters.  With the Cold War over, are they still the same cold-hearted monsters?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;

To apply this ideology to current social issues, I see more and more people thinking that: "People are poor because they are lazy" and "Homeless people choose to be homeless".  I guess I can't blame these misguided folks.  These delusions comfort us and help us avoid the painful realities that we encounter daily (especially when you walk down Telegraph).  After all, indifference is a lot easier to deal with than empathy. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;

So in conclusion, I don't feel that life is black or white at all... that there really is no good or evil.  Rather, we live in a world of indistinguishable gray, where there are always someone else's shoes to step into.  But to answer the question... in spite of what I wrote earlier... I would have to say that *prepare for controversial statement* the Bush Administration is amongst the most "evil" things in existence.  I would also like to note that I don't really believe in the word "evil"... especially in the sense that the administration has used it (i.e. evil-doers).  Everyone has the capability for evil, and we also all have the capability for good. It's just that I have yet to see the latter capability realized in this administration.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>9a</number>
		<answer>
		</answer>
	</question>
	<question>
		<number>9b</number>
		<answer>
		</answer>
	</question>

</profile>