<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<profile>
 <question>
  <number>0</number>
  <answer></answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>1</number>
  <answer>
   Emi Ikkanda
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>2</number>
  <answer>
   Art and English - 2 for the price of 1!
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>3</number>
  <answer>
   Uh
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>4</number>
  <answer>
   Currently UN-single
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>5</number>
  <answer>
   I run really slowly.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>6</number>
  <answer>
   I love rice because it's so fluffy and steamy and delicious.  And it goes with everything!
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>7</number>
  <answer>
   Free food?
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>8</number>
  <answer>
   To be elected the coolest person ever.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>9</number>
  <answer>
   Ah, I think the more pressing question is Who are YOU?  And, are YOU going to finish that?
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>10</number>
  <answer>
   Wild Monkey.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>11</number>
  <answer>
   Probably the Wild Monkey, depending on whether he successfully knifed the Rocky Balboa and the US Mint.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>12</number>
  <answer>
   We should all be born old and grow young.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>13</number>
  <answer>
   I could say water, but instead, I will say they drink ... dry cleaning.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>14</number>
  <answer>
   Underdogs are cool.  Generally, I take the side of liberals, small fuzzy animal lovers, movie freaks, painters, playwrites, wreckless writers, Daily Show admirers, Francophiles, adoptive San Francisco natives, foodies, slam poets, the indie music elite, the guiltily pleasured Gilmore Girls fans, the alt rockers, the closeted techno fans, the people-who-are-terrified-of-not-knowing-what-to-do-with-their-lives, the sorta-actors of the planet, the Strong Bad e-mailers, the people-who-laugh-at-the-wrong-time, and of course, I take the side of ALL THAT IS AWESOME.
  </answer>
 </question>
</profile>
