<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<profile>
 <question>
  <number>0</number>
  <answer></answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>1</number>
  <answer>
   Rick Kitagawa
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>2</number>
  <answer>
   Integrative Biology
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>3</number>
  <answer>
   Asian American Studies
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>4</number>
  <answer>
   I'd like one?  Today's date?  9/15/04.  Birthdate? 07/26/83.  Hot date? Yes I am.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>5</number>
  <answer>
   American of Japanese Ancestry
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>6</number>
  <answer>
   The people in it, our audience, the friendships made through it, and the few times people have come up to me randomly to congratulate me on a show.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>7</number>
  <answer>
   I'm looking for friendship, fame, and to meet women through it.  Oh yeah, and to fight the misrepresentation and underrepresentation of Asian Americans in the media.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>8</number>
  <answer>
   To do something worthwhile.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>9</number>
  <answer>
   I am a poet, a lover, a student, a writer, a leader, a party-goer, a musician, an athlete, a friend, an enemy, a performer, a boy.  Most importantly, I am me, and that's all that really matters.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>10</number>
  <answer>
   My money goes to the monkey, hands down.  You gotta support your relatives, you know.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>11</number>
  <answer>
   It would be a combination of the Cal Nutball Team, Kittymeowmeow, and the ladies of the FHS 2001 Aca Dec Team.  Together, we'd totally be unstoppable.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>12</number>
  <answer>
   To be born while your mother is skydiving into the middle of the Superbowl while protesting the war.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>13</number>
  <answer>
   Water.  But since I don't like this question, I'm going to answer: Who is your favorite comic book character?  Spider-Man, hands down.  Although Venom and Wolverine tie for a close second.
  </answer>
 </question>
</profile>
