<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<profile>
 <question>
  <number>0</number>
  <answer></answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>1</number>
  <answer>
   Sean Cardeno, but you may call me Seany? if you get my permission. Oh yeah, Seany Boy naturally derives from that nickname too.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>2</number>
  <answer>
   Mass Com
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>3</number>
  <answer></answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>4</number>
  <answer>
   December 9.  Remember it!
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>5</number>
  <answer>
   Filipino and proud.  I?m probably part Hyrulian too.  Props if you get that joke.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>6</number>
  <answer>
   The friggin people! The facking creativity! The two are intertwined and impossible to separate! Someone once said that Theatre Rice is the best group of people at Cal.  I find myself agreeing with that person more and more every time we all meet.  Awwww huh? Warm and fuzzies all around.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>7</number>
  <answer>
   I am looking for an outlet to express myself? What a generic thing to say.  But ?tis true!  I can?t deny the world of my beautiful mind any longer! Muahahhaha!
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>8</number>
  <answer>
   I desire to have awesome super powers of flight and strength and agility, but not to use for good.  Instead, I will use them to bully people to VOTE FOR KERRY!! Haha, just kidding. I?m not even that political.  I don?t really watch VOTE FOR KERRY!! the news or anything.  Subliminal enough for ya? In all seriocity though?. super powers would rock.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>9</number>
  <answer>
   I am? a Matrix-thinking, Anime-geeking, superhero-daydreaming, videogame-obsessing, friends-chilling, music-appreciating, Ricer-living, girlfriend-loving? modofocko.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>10</number>
  <answer></answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>11</number>
  <answer>
   My sidekick would have to be Barb.  I?m Awesome#1, she?s Awesome#2. =P The world doesn?t stand a chance?
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>12</number>
  <answer>
   You know when the oceans divide, eighty-three volcanoes erupt simultaneously, and six billion people are lost in a riotous frenzy over your coming into the world?? Yeah? it?s more dramatic and awesome than that.
  </answer>
 </question>
 <question>
  <number>13</number>
  <answer>
   They drink Mike Cao?s Arizona Iced Tea. Yet another inside joke. Trick!
  </answer>
 </question>
</profile>
